(Leonard:)With a hologram? Nice.
(Leonard:)Hey, do you see this?
(Sheldon:)I'm in the matrix, Leonard,
I see everything.
You gotta be kidding me.
You friended Stuart on Facebook?
- I thought you didn't like Facebook.
- Don't be silly.
(Sheldon:)I'm a fan of anything that tries to replace
actual human contact.
(Raj:)Please. You're looking at Facebook
to find out how their date went.
(Sheldon:)Really? You think I care if a man...
...what, "Shared a pumpkin latte
with a dynamite lady"?
- You're so full of it.
- You're free to believe whatever you like.
(Sheldon:)And unfriend Rajesh Koothrappali.
(Raj:)You unfriended me? Seriously?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah. Now he's gonna miss
all those great updates like:
"l can't believe I waited this Iong...
...to make my own potpourri." Ha, ha.
Why don't you acknowledge
you have feelings for Amy...
...and don't want her going out
with other men?
(Sheldon:)And unfriend Leonard Hofstadter.
Here's a radical thought. Go old school.
Challenge Stuart to a fight.